Guide to the Edward Bradford Titchener papers,1887-1940.
Titchener, Edward Bradford papers, 1887-1940
- Correspondence
  - J. Alvarey Pastor to EBT, 6/8/22 (Box 4)
  - G. Stanley Han to EBT, 6/15/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Pillsbury, 6/24/22 (Box 4)
  - T. A. Hunter to EBT, 6/27/22 (Box 4)
  - M. Fukushima to EBT, 6/28/22 (Box 4)
  - lyman Low to EBT, 7/5/22 (Box 4)
  - lyman Low to EBT, 7/22/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Feldraan, 8/2/22 (Box 4)
  - Elizabeth to EBT, 8/22/22 (Box 4)
  - R. Lisbonne to EBT, 9/18/22 (Box 4)
  - H. iesage to EBT, 9/25/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 9/28/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to A. H. Nelson, 9/28/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 9/29/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. 0. Oldman, 9/29/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to T. A. Hunter, 10/5/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 10/5/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Howard C. Warren, 10/5/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to M. H. Lesage, 10/6/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 10/7/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lord Frederic Hamilton, 10/10/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Sincere Trading Company, 10/11/22 (Box 4)
  - Margaret McNaught to EBTEnd, letter of resignation as Commissioner of Elementary schools in California, 10/11/22 (Box 4)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 10/11/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Lesage, 10/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Franklin 0. Smith, 10/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Pillsbury, 10/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 10/13/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to President G. Stanley Hall, 10/13/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 10/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Elder Coin and Curio Corporation, 10/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 10/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. McDougall, 10/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. B. English, 10/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C* H. Stoelting, 10/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. Stanley Hall, 10/16/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 10/17/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. L. DiMr.aick, 10/17/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. Stanley Hall, 10/17/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 10/17/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. L. Dimmick, 10/17/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Raymond Dodge, 10/18/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to M. F. Washburn, 10/18/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Robinson, 10/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to L. Clements, 10/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Margaret McNaught, 10/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. C. H. Griffitts, 10/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Miss Digain Williams, 10/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. y. H. Ward, 10/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. C. S. Myers, 10/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor A. Michotle, 10/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 10/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Frank Angell, 10/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. A. Poynder, 10/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. McDougall, 10/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Ernest E. Rayner, 10/20/22 (Box 4)
  - John B. Watson, 10/21/22 (Box 4)
  - Rowland Wood to EBT, 10/24/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ruckmick, 10/26/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman H. Low, 10/26/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to the Milton Bradley Company, 10/28/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Carl Fischer Musical Company, 10/28/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 10/28/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Sangfeld, 10/28/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Clark L. Howell, 10/28/22 (Box 4)
  - R. A. Tsanoff to EBT, 10/28/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Frank Angell, 10/31/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 10/31/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Max F. Meyer, 10/31/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. C. H. Stoelting, 10/31/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Fisk Teachers Agency, 10/31/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 10/31/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. H. E. Starr, 11/1/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 11/2/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Forest Diramick, 11/7/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to S. J. Theodore, ll/7/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lord Frederic Hamilton, 11/7/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 11/9/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Howard C. Warren, 11/9/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to William C. Foster, 11/9/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Forrest Dimmick, 11/10/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Forrest Dimmick, 11/11/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to R. A. Tsanoff, 11/11/22 (Box 4)
  - Tomi Wada to EBT, 11/12/22 (Box 4)
  - J. E. Creighton to EBT, 11/13/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to T. A. Hunter, 11/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to T. A. Hunter, 11/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Revd. Henry Braddock, 11/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Miss May Braddock, 11/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Robinson, 11/16/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 11/16/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. P. Andrews, 11/17/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Norman Gamer on, 11/17/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to M. lokoyama, 11/18/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman H. Low, 11/21/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 11/21/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 11/21/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to William C. Foster, 11/21/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Forrest L. Dimmick, 11/21/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Forrest L. DimmickEncl. report on experimental results, 11/21/22 (Box 4)
  - John B. Watson to EBT, 11/21/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Frank Angell, 11/22/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Librarian, University of Edinburgh, 11/22/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 11/22/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 11/22/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Carroll C. Pratt, 11/22/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 11/22/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Alien Art Studios, 11/23/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to John B. Watson, 11/23/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to L. R. Geissler, 11/23/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 11/23/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Treman King and Company, 11/23/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor A. A. Alien, 11/24/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Florence Richardson-Robinson, 11/24/22 (Box 4)
  - Lyman Low to EBT, 11/28/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. S. Sangfeld (fragment undated), 1922 ?? (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 12/1/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 12/1/22- (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Santo de Sanctis, 12/2/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Samuel W. Fernberger, 12/2/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Zing Yang Kuo, 12/2/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 12/2/22 (Box 4)
  - R. R. Smith to EBT, 12/4/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 12/5/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 12/5/22 (Box 4)
  - John B. Watson to EBT, 12/6/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. F. H. Ward, 12/6/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. Russell Bichowsky, 12/6/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 12/6/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. H. Post, 12/6/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor William F. Book, 12/6/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Torai Wada, 12/7/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 12/7/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 12/8/22 - (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor H. Lesage, 12/8/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 12/8/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 12/8/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 12/8/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Andrew McPherson, 12/8/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. Strunk Jr., 12/8/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to 0. G. Guerlac, 12/8/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to National Geographic Magazine, 12/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Wilm, 12/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to A. H. Smith, 12/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor J. R. Schramm, 12/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. B. H. Blackwell, 12/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. A. S. Rogers, 12/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Joseph F. Hickey, 12/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to George Hecht, 12/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Madison Bentley, 12/12/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Frank Angell, 12/13/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 12/13/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Charles H. Gillespie, 12/13/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. H. B. Davis, 12/13/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Miss Eleonore Wundt, 12/13/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 12/13/22 (Box 4)
  - H. Ambronn (?) to EBT, 12/14/22 German (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. A. Poynder, 12/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. C. Nicholson, 12/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to librarian, University of Halle, 12/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to R. J. Roddy, 12/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 12/14/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. E. A. Culler, 12/15/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. C. H. Stoelting, 12/15/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Gustav Fock, 12/15/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. L. A. Fuertes, 12/16/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to James L. Munsell, 12/16/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dean C. E. Bens on, 12/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor 3. W. Fernberger, 12/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor H. 3. Langfeld, 12/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor 0. G. Guerlac, 12/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. A. 3. Rogers, 12/19/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Raymond Dodge, 12/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 12/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. C. Bartlett, 12/20/22 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Gustav Fock, 12/20/22 (Box 4)
  - C. S. Myers to EBT, 12/20/22 (Box 4)
  - George Alien and Un in to EBT, 12/31/22 (Box 4)
  - Manuscript, 1922 (Box 4)
  - 1923 (Box 4)
  - Mimeographed statement, The First Year of the Psychological Corporation, 1/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to P. Jones, 1/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to T. A. Hunter, 1/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 1/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 1/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 1/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 1/5/23 (Box 4)
  - Mrs.. G. P. Baker to EBT, 1/15/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Vice President, First National Bank, Ithaca, N. Y., 1/18/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Howard C. Warren, 1/25/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. A. A. Roback, 1/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Macmillan, 1/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoetling, 1/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. E. Ferree, 1/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to A. 3. Rogers, 1/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 1/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 1/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Win. L. Westermann, 1/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Charles C. Parker, 1/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dean C. E. Benson, 1/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoetling, 1/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Tsanoff, 2/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Alice H. Sullivan, 2/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. A. j. Snow, 2/1/23 (Box 4)
  - Julien J. Champenois to EBT, 2/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 2/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 2/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Howard C. Warren, 2/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 2/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H., 2/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Ai H. Vanderlip, 2/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor M. S. Slaughter, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Wm. L. Westermann, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. J. Champenois, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to 0. G. Guerlac, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Baker, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 2/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 2/6/23 (Box 4)
  - John B. Watson to EBT, 2/6/23 (Box 4)
  - J. D. M. Ford to 0. Guerlac, 2/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor G. Stirring, 2/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dean of Granduate School, Cornell University, 2/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Samuel Fernberger, 2/8/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. Stanley Ha11, 2/8/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to John B. Watson, 2/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. O. Weber, 2/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mrs.. C. W. Perky, 2/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor George F. Arps, 2/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoetling, 2/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to HaMr.aond, 2/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to 0. G. Guerlac, 2/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor N. R. Pugh, 2/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Miss Hickman, 2/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor J. Q. Adams, 2/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Hoy, 2/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Miss Jacobs, 2/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Wm. L. Westermann, 2/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. A. A. Roback, 2/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Paul T. Young, 2/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Thomas Elder, 2/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 2/13/23 (Box 4)
  - * Insertions made because of additional material received. See accession sheets. (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. P. T. Young, 2/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 2/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. C. C. Kleber, 2/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. E. Merriam, 2/14/23 (Box 4)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 2/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. E. Merriam, 2/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. William H. Boyd, 2/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Paul T. Young, 2/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. L. Dimmick, 2/22/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. L. Dimmick, 22/22/23 (Box 4)
  - John B. Watson to EBT, 2/26/23 (Box 4)
  - C. H. Stoelting to EBT, 3/3/23 (Box 4)
  - H. Bishop to EBT, 3/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 3/6/23 (Box 4)
  - P. H. Klemm to EBT, 3/9/23 German (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor L. L. Berhard, 3/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 3/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 3/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 3/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to L. T. Troland, 3/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 3/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. M. J. Zigler, 3/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to R. P. Angier, 3/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Raymond Dodge, 3/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. P. Boswell, 3/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 3/15/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. A. Rieckmick, 3/15/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. J. Rich, 3/15/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. F. Shepard, 3/15/23 (Box 4)
  - * Insertions made because of acid, material rec'd. See Accession Sheets. (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. S. Robinson, 3/15/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor F. L. Dimmick, 3/15/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor F. L. Dimmick, 3/15/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Miss May Braddock, 3/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. A. Boyd, 3/23/23 (Box 4)
  - John B. Watson, 3/28/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to John B. Watson, 4/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Franz Boas, 4/10/23 (Box 4)
  - Seth Wakeman to EBT, 4/11/23 (Box 4)
  - Schenker and Co. to EBT, 4/12/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dalltobach, 4/17/23 (Box 4)
  - H. 3. to EBT, 4/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Raymond Dodge, 4/19/23 (Box 4)
  - R. S. Whipple to EBT, 4/20/23 (Box 4)
  - C. W. Campbell to Professor P. Nafe, 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to S., 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. R. Crosland, 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Wn. Elliot Griffis, 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Zimmermann, 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Zimmermann, 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. B. Pillsbury, 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Miss Jacobs, 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to The Secretary, Radcliffe College, Cambridge, Mass., 5/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. I. Cranford, 5/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Rowland Wood, 5/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to George Alien and Unwin, 5/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Christiance-Dudley Pharmacy, 5/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. H. B. Davis, 5/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Kimball Young, 5/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to R. A. Tsanoff, 5/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. 0. Oldman, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. M. S. Midjo, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dallenbach, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Lancaster, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Raymond Dodge, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. A. Hamilton, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Rich, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. G. J. Rich, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. G. Bull, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. E. Van Natta, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Livingston Farrand, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Arthur E. Iredell, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor L. L. Bernard, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Max F. Meyer, 5/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Carl Witmer, 5/4/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. S. Robinson, 5/4/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lucia, 5/4/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor A. J. Snow, 5/4/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. C. Robertson, 5/4/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. I. Crawford, 5/4/23 (Box 4)
  - John B. Watson to EBT, 5/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor L. R. Geissler, 5/8/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Howard C. Warren, 5/8/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. S. Foster, 5/16/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Howard C. Warren, 5/16/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Miss Isabel C. Robertson, 5/16/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Karl Dallanbach, 5/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. H. H. Crum, 5/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H., 5/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 5/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor H. C. Warren, 5/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 5/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Alice Sullivan, 5/18/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 5/18/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. A. L. Rose, 5/22/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 5/22/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. A. S. Daniel, 5/22/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to A. S. Osborn, 5/22/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. M. J. Zigler, 5/22/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Shaw Publishing Company, 5/22/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 5/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. B. H. Blackwell, 5/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor J. T. Quarles, 5/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 5/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 5/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 5/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Edward T. Newell, 5/24/23 (Box 4)
  - L. R. Geissler to EBT, 5/25/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. T. L. Elder, 5/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. M. S. Midjo, 5/29/23 (Box 4)
  - Gordon Allport to EBT, 5/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 5/31/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor John E. Anderson, 6/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. J. McKeen Cattell, 6/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Howard C. Warren, 6/7/23 (Box 4)
  - Frederick Ebell Fiske to EBT, 6/18/23 (Box 4)
  - L. S. Gould (?) to EBT, 6/19/23 (Box 4)
  - Karl Dallenbach to EBT, 6/30/23 (Box 4)
  - H. Henderson to EBT, 7/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Forrest DimniickEncl. index of the American Journal of Psychology Vol.I-XXXI, 8/22/23 (Box 4)
  - James Angell to EBT, 8/25/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. B. Bool, 10/4/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to T. L. Elder, 10/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 10/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to L. Clements, 10/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mrs.. C. Ladd Franklin, 10/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to the Macmillan Company, 10/6/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, Clark University Library, 10/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Frank Angell, 10/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to George Connelly, 10/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 10/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Max Wocher and Son, 10/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to A. A. Roback, 10/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Josiah Morse, 10/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Marie Neri, 10/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 10/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 10/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor H. C. Warren, 10/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 10/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 10/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. H. Winch, 10/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 10/11/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. S. H. Self, 10/11/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. 0. Oldman, 10/11/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 10/11/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 10/12/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 10/12/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to the Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 10/12/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to the Macmillan Company, 10/12/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor H. Lesage, 10/12/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 10/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 10/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 10/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 10/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Martin L. Reymert, 10/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 10/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Howard C. Warren, 10/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to A. N. Marquis & Company, 10/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 10/18/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 10/18/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor C. V. Tower, 10/18/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Secretary, Bureau of American Ethnology, 10/18/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Josiah Morse, 10/18/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 10/18/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 10/19/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Rosewell P. Angler, 10/19/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 10/19/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Howland Wood, 10/19/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 10/19/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 10/19/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to the Regina Company, 10/19/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 10/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 10/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. F. Dashiell, 10/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 10/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Frank Angell, 10/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to A. J. Snow, 10/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Ray Simpson, 10/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Rudolph Kohler, 10/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Spindler & Hoyer, 10/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Herr E. Zimmermann, 10/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. F. Hickey, 10/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. J. Bun, 10/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Doubleday Page & Co., 10/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Roger & Gallet, 10/23/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Foster P. Boswell, 10/24/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 10/24/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 10/24/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. John Grant, 10/24/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 10/24/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor B. von Hornbostel, 10/25/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to George Alien and Unwin, 10/25/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 10/25/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Mason D. Gray, 10/25/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Bishop, 10/25/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Ballenbach, 10/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 10/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Raymond Dodge, 10/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor D. C. Rogers, 10/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. S. Robinson, 10/26/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. B. Pillsbury, 10/27/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Grace K. Adams, 10/2?/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 10/27/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 10/27/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. B. Pillsbury, 10/27/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Rudolph Kohler, 10/27/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 10/27/23 -missing (Box 4)
  - C. V. Tower to EBT, 10/28/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to & H. Jordan, 10/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Sangfeld, 10/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to A. C. Reid, 10/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 10/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor George Humphrey, 10/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Macmillan Company, 10/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Max Meyer, 10/30/23 (Box 4)
  - L. N. Wilson to EBT, 10/31/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. M. J. Zigler, 10/31/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Raymond Dodge, 10/31/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. V. Tower, 10/31/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 10/31/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 10/31/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 11/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H., 11/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. A. de Hostos, 11/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 11/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. James D. We inland, 11/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Wilhelm Engelmann, 11/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Robert W. Bruce, 11/1/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. F. Hickey, 11/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to D. C. Rogers, 11/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 11/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 11/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. J. Rich, 11/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 11/2/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Walter M. Horton, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. J. Walter Fewkes, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. S. Robinson, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor L. B. Hoistington, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. G. Bishop, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. S. Weld, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to S. Feldman, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lovell Bixly, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to K. M. Dallenbach, 11/3/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. S. Myers, 11/6/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Charles Parker, 11/6/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to F. L. Wells, 11/6/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 11/6/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to R. P. Angler, 11/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Walter Horton, 11/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 11/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 11/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to R M. Ogden, 11/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 11/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to L. L. Bernard, 11/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. H. Lundholm, 11/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 11/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 11/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. C. c. Pratt, 11/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor L. T. Troland, 11/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. J. Rich, 11/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. S. Foster, 11/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. V. Bingham, 11/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to K. S. Lashley, 11/9/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. F. L. Dimmick, 11/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to W. B. Pillsbury, 11/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. F. Shepard, 11/10/23 (Box 4)